http://www.enviresearch.com/privacy-policy

skip to main contentAbout usContact UsNewsPrivacy PolicyCookie InfoSite MapEnviresearch FoundationPortuguese OfficeTestimonialsCase Studies Go to TwitterGo to LinkedInEnviresearch Home PageHomePlant Protection productsPlant Protection Products UK Drainflow modellingEnvironmental fateEcotoxicologyEfficacyHuman healthBiocidesBiocidesEnvironmental fateEcotoxicologyEfficacyHuman healthREACHREACHEnvironmental fateEcotoxicologyHuman healthPharmaceuticalsPharmaceuticalsEnvironmental fateEcotoxicologyVeterinaryVeterinaryEnvironmental fateEcotoxicologyHuman healthEnvironmentEndocrine disruptionAcre WebinarBrexitAged SorptionEnviresearch Home PagePrivacy PolicyPrivacy notice re your personal data:What we needEnviresearch Ltd will be what’s known as the ‘Controller’ of the personal data you provide to us. We only collect basic personal data about you which does not include any special types of information or location based information. This does however include name and contact details such as address (work or home, as provided), email, phone number etc, and any personal information that you openly tell us.Why we need itWe need to know basic personal data in order to conduct our business and maintain contact and effective relationships with our partners, suppliers and customers. We will not collect any personal data from you we do not need in order to conduct our business.What we do with itWhere it is necessary for the conduct of our business the information described above may be shared between Enviresearch Ltd (of 77 Dunholme Road, Newcastle upon Tyne, NE4 6XD; UK company no. 4292592) and any wholly owned subsidiary companies of Enviresearch Ltd (as of April 2018 we have one such subsidiary, Enviresearch Portugal Unipessoal Lda, of Rua Fernando Pessoa, N.º 319, 2.º C, Sassoeiros, Carcavelos 2775-515 Carcavelos; Portuguese company no. 514556021) who are located within the UK or the EU. No other third parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so, or unless you specifically consent to this during the course of the provision of our services.If you are a business or an employee of a business we may use your contact details for marketing purposes to send you information or offers that we believe would be of particular interest to you and that we think you may reasonably expect to receive from us, based upon the legitimate commercial interests of our business. You may opt out of such communications at any time using the contact details given below.All the personal data we process is processed by our staff and workers in the country where they are based, which will not be outside of the UK or the EU; however for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information may also be located on servers within the European Union and the United States of America.We have a Data Protection regime in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data.How long we keep itWe will normally keep your data for 6 years after which time it will be destroyed.What we would also like to do with itIf you give your explicit consent we would also like to use your name and email address to discuss opportunities for work, give news about Enviresearch and to maintain ongoing relations. This information may be shared with our wholly owned subsidiary Enviresearch Portugal Unipessoal Lda, who are located in Portugal, but is not shared with any other third parties except with your explicit advance consent. You can withdraw your consent at any time via phone or email (details below).What are your rights?You can request at any time to see the information that we hold on you, and you can also request to have it corrected or deleted. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact us and we will investigate the matter.If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).You can contact us at any time at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. or call 0191 2430687.Go to TwitterGo to LinkedIn
Contact
Enviresearch Ltd34 Grainger Park RoadNewcastle upon Tyne NE4 8RYTelephone: +44 (0)191 243 0687Email: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Further Information
About usMeet the TeamNewsSelect LanguageEnglishAfrikaansAlbanianArabicArmenianAzerbaijaniBasqueBelarusianBulgarianCatalanChinese (Simplified)Chinese (Traditional)CroatianCzechDanishDutchEstonianFilipinoFinnishFrenchGalicianGeorgianGermanGreekHaitian CreoleHebrewHindiHungarianIcelandicIndonesianIrishItalianJapaneseKoreanLatvianLithuanianMacedonianMalayMalteseNorwegianPersianPolishPortugueseRomanianRussianSerbianSlovakSlovenianSpanishSwahiliSwedishThaiTurkishUkrainianUrduVietnameseWelshYiddishHomePlant Protection productsPlant Protection Products UK Drainflow modellingEnvironmental fateEcotoxicologyEfficacyHuman healthBiocidesBiocidesEnvironmental fateEcotoxicologyEfficacyHuman healthREACHREACHEnvironmental fateEcotoxicologyHuman healthPharmaceuticalsPharmaceuticalsEnvironmental fateEcotoxicologyVeterinaryVeterinaryEnvironmental fateEcotoxicologyHuman healthEnvironmentEndocrine disruptionAcre WebinarBrexitAged SorptionAbout usOur TeamJames GarrattChristina LyeCiara HopeJosé SobreiroLaura Wildsmith Rachel GillScott WatsonHelen PyeChris McGurk Steven Banks, PhDCharles HazleriggSabine BeulkeWendy Van BeinumLouise PopeScott HawleyNeil GrahamEmma TilsonAlice Tagliati, MSc Nick MartinBrenden WardJenny AbbottContact UsNewsPrivacy PolicyCookie InfoSite MapEnviresearch FoundationPortuguese OfficeTestimonialsCase Studies
